

TIARA SARI DEWI

Address: Bandung, West Java, Indonesia 40288

Phone: +62-888-1870-047

Email: tiarasd.work@gmail.com
Website: www.tiarasdewi.com

SUMMARY

I specialize in building modern, responsive web applications using React.js and Next.js. With over three years of experience, I've contributed to a wide range of projects from dynamic landing pages to complex web platforms. While my core strength lies in frontend development, I'm currently expanding my skillset as a Fullstack Developer, gaining valuable experience in backend technologies and API integration.

AREA OF EXPERTISE

Frontend Development HTML, CSS (SCSS), JS/TS

React & Next.js

Responsive Design

Cross-browser Compatibility

SEO & Accessibility

Component-Based Architecture

RESTful API Integration Version Control (Git)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer, Greeneration Foundation

Jan 2024 - Present

- Fixing bugs and performing maintenance on all GF products.
- Optimizing user experience.
- Developed and migrated the company profile website from WordPress to Next.js, improving performance, SEO, and maintainability.

Frontend Engineer, Greeneration Foundation

May 2023 - Dec 2023

- Developed and migrated GFDP donation platform frontend from Codelgniter to Next.js, improving performance, SEO, and maintainability.
- Collaborating with the IT team to maintain GFDP donation platform

Web Developer, Senja Solutions

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

 Collaborating with the development team to develop, fix and maintain Arrow Checkout website and shopify

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering

Sept 2015 - Mar 2020

Widyatama University, Bandung

- · Major in Information Technology.
- Thesis on "Implementation of the Content-Based Method as a Mobile-Based Laptop Recommendation System Using the K-Nearest Neighbor Algorithm".

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: Bahasa Indonesia, English.
- Certifications: TOEIC® Listening & Reading Total: 935 (Listening: 480 / Reading: 455).
- Activities: Actively participated in the Informatics Engineering Student Association as Deputy
 Head of the Human Resources Department, responsible for organizing recruitment for laboratory
 assistants and teaching assistants.